Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Lamar Alexander Papers
1953-2017
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0734
617 linear_feet
- Series I: Early Years & Higher Education
  - Boy Scout Materials, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scout Pamphlets – circa, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scout and Merit Cards – circa, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scout Requirements Handbook, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scout Handbook for Patrol Leaders, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Handbook for Boys, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scout Explorer Manual, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Boys State – Boys Nation Alumni Correspondence Files, 1957-1958 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Boys State – Boys Nation Alumni Correspondence Files, 1957-1958 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Boys State – Correspondence, 1957 June-1958 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Boys State – Correspondence on Alexander’s Election to Governor of Boys State, 1957 July-September (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Boys State – Delegate Press Clippings, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Boys State – Volunteer Boys State Certificates, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Boys State – Signed Al Gore Sr. Photograph – circa, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Boys State – Elect Lamar Alexander Governor of Boys’ State Sheets, circa 1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Boys State – Certificate of Graduation, 1957 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Boys State – Important Boys Nation Members and Statistics, 1958 June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Boys State – Session Materials, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Boys State – The Volunteer Newspaper, 1957 June, 1958 June (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boys State – Instructions, Rules and Regulations for Boys Nation Senators, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Boys State – Postcards, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Boys State – Directory, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Boys State – Awards and Certificates, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Boys State – Handbook – circa, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Boys State – Voice of Democracy, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Boys State – Volunteer Boys State Schedule, 1957 June 10-17, July (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Boys State – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Boys State – Speech Materials, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Boys State – U.S. Capitol Tickets, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Boys State – Elect Alexander Flyer, circa 1957 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Term Papers and Themes, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Key Club, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Junior Red Cross Materials, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - High School Materials, 1955-1959 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - High School Materials, 1955-1959 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vote Tallies – circa, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - National Westminster Fellowship Assembly Documents, 1957 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - National Westminster Fellowship Assembly Documents, 1957 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Church Documents, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - East Tennessee Band and Orchestra Association Program, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Higher Education – Vanderbilt Fraternity Bids, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Higher Education – Family Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Higher Education – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Higher Education – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Higher Education – Speeches, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Higher Education – Letter from FCC Engineer, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Higher Education – NYU Financial Documents, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Higher Education – Articles Written by Alexander, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Higher Education – NYU – Miscellaneous Saved Materials, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Higher Education – Hustler Application Writing Samples, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Higher Education – Vanderbilt Hustler Photographs – circa, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Higher Education – NYU Lists, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Series II: Family Files
  - Family History Documents, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - “Brief History of Tapoco and the Great Smoky Country”, 1950 May (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Andrew L. Alexander Correspondence, Clippings, and Speeches, 1954-1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Parent’s Files, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Alexander Family Photographs Collected by Lamar – circa, 1950-circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Flo Alexander – circa, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration Clippings, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Baby Photograph of Lamar Alexander, 1940 August (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mother’s Early Years Scrapbook, 1940-1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photographs from Alexander’s Secretary of Education Swearing-in Ceremony, 1991 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Early Governor Scrapbook, 1978-1980 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Early Governor Scrapbook, 1978-1980 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mother’s Early Years and High School Scrapbook – circa, 1940-circa 1958 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mother’s Early Years and High School Scrapbook – circa, 1940-circa 1958 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mother’s High School Scrapbook – circa, 1954-circa 1958 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mother’s High School Scrapbook – circa, 1954-circa 1958 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Mother’s NYU Scrapbook, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Grandmother’s Scrapbook of Correspondence and Photos from Honey, circa 1970-circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1972-1980 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1972-1980 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1980 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1980 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1980 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mother’s Binder of Photographs, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1992 (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1992 (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 January-February (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 February-March (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 February-March (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 April (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 March-August (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 March-August (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 May-June (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 May-June (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 September-December (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Mother’s Secretary of Education Scrapbook, 1991 September-December (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Series III: Early Political Career
  - Sub-series A: Personal Papers
    - Resume, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Howard Baker Campaign Realia, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Dortch Oldham Campaign Realia, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Nat Winston Campaign Realia, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Winnfield Dunn Campaign Realia, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Jane Hardaway Campaign Realia, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Nixon Campaign Realia, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Magazines kept by Alexander, 1956-1969 (1 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Magazines kept by Alexander, 1956-1969 (2 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Magazines kept by Alexander, 1956-1969 (3 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Magazines kept by Alexander, 1956-1969 (4 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Personal Files – Westminster Church, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Personal Files – X-Z, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Personal Files – Photocopy of House Joint Resolution Number 35 Commending Alexander, 1971 March 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Personal Files – Presidential Campaign Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Personal Files – Election Results, 1972 August 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Personal Files – Tennessee Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Personal Files – Pocket Diary, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Personal Files – Clyde York, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Personal Files – Washington Financial Reports, 1973 July 30 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Personal Files – The Tennessee Report, 1973 July 27 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Personal Files – Metro Center Update, 1973 August (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Personal Files – Maryville High School Senior Day Program, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Personal Files – Tourmobile Discount Coupon, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Personal Files – Tennessee Politics and Government – A Handbook for Citizen Involvement, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Personal Files – Republican National Finance Committee Pamphlet, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Personal Files – The College Republican, 1973 February 26 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Personal Files – News from Tennessee Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Personal Files – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Personal Files – Fireproof Insurance Claims, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Personal Files – Proffitt, Dave, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Personal Files – R, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Personal Files – Ripon Society, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Personal Files – Renter Check, 1973 December 11 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Personal Files – Rodgers, Joe M., 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Personal Files – S, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Personal Files – Senate and House Committees, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Personal Files – Speaking Engagements, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Personal Files – T, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Personal Files – U-V, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Personal Files – W, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Personal Files – Washington Financial Reports, 1973 July 16 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Personal Files – White, Clifton F., 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Personal Files – White, David, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Personal Files – Wilkinson, Jay, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Private Practice – Manual for Directors of the Vanderbilt Alumni Association, 1975 July (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Private Practice – Correspondence – M, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Private Practice – Correspondence – N, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Private Practice – Correspondence – W, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Private Practice – Maryville College Files, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Private Practice – National Council on Crime and Delinquency Files, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Private Practice – Rev R. Rankin File, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Private Practice – Campaign Finance, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Private Practice – An Unofficial Compilation of the Federal Election Laws, 1976 May 17 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Private Practice – Correspondence – X-Z, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Private Practice – U.S.D.C. Rules for Eastern District, 1960-1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Private Practice – Interoffice Memorandums, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Private Practice – Ensworth School Estate Planning Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Private Practice – Forms, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Private Practice – “Private Sector Recreation Development in Tennessee – Impacts and Prospects”, 1975 December (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Private Practice – Viewpoint – Statements, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Private Practice – Viewpoint – Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Private Practice – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Private Practice – Miscellaneous Law Firm Materials, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Private Practice – Alumni Association of Vanderbilt University Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Sub-series B: Political Activities
    - Baker Campaign – 1966 Campaign Materials, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Baker Campaign – Baker Speech at Opening of Campaign for Senate, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Baker Campaign – Election Analysis, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Baker Campaign – Campaign Correspondence, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Baker Campaign – Knoxville Baker TV Spots, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Baker Campaign – Invitations and Cards, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Baker Campaign – Young Tennesseans for Baker Organization Manual, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Baker Campaign – Revenue Sharing, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Baker Campaign – Schedules, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Baker Campaign – Leg Work, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Baker Campaign – Financial and Campaign Numbers, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Baker Campaign – Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Baker Campaign – Miscellaneous Notes, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Baker Campaign – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Baker Campaign – Reelection Campaign Materials, 1971-1972 (1 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Baker Campaign – Reelection Campaign Materials, 1971-1972 (2 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Baker Campaign – Reelection Campaign Materials, 1971-1972 (3 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Baker Campaign – Baker for Senate Campaign Notes and Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Baker Campaign – Senator Howard Baker Jr. Personal File, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Nixon Aide – Youth for Nixon Mock Political Convention Manual – circa, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Nixon Aide – Campaign Materials, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Nixon Aide – Documents Saved from Press Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Nixon Aide – Nixon for President 1968 Convention Telephone Directory, 1968 July 31 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Nixon Aide – Staff Notes and Statistics, 1968 October 4 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Nixon Aide – Calendar, 1968 September (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Nixon Aide – Inaugural Committee Materials, 1969 January (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Nixon Aide – Personal File, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Nixon Aide – Memos to the President, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Nixon Aide – “The President’s Official Family” – circa, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Nixon Aide – Harlow Regrets Notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Nixon Aide – Jokes, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Nixon Aide – Members of the White House Staff, 1970 February (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Nixon Aide – Goddess of Beauty Letter, 1970 March 3 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Nixon Aide – Alexander Invitation to be Guest Speaker at the 4th Congressional District Republican Committee Meeting, 1970 March 26-31 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Nixon Aide – Kentucky Youth Conference, 1970 July (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Nixon Aide – Vice Presidential Campaigning Materials, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Nixon Aide – Brock Report, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Nixon Aide – Birthday Wishes, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Nixon Aide – Inauguration Invitations and Programs, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Nixon Aide – Invitations, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Nixon Aide – Cards from President Nixon, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Nixon Aide – Untitled Speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Nixon Aide – Untitled Notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Nixon Aide – Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Nixon Aide – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Nixon Aide – Salute to the President Dinner Souvenir, 1971 November 9 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Inaugural Ball, 1971 January (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (1 of 7) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (2 of 7) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (3 of 7) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (4 of 7) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (5 of 7) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (6 of 7) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 1969-1971 (7 of 7) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Revised Grand Design for the Dunn Campaign, circa 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Inaugural Ball Invitations, 1971 January (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Inaugural Committee, 1970 December (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – John Jay Hooker, 1970 April-October (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Campaign Ribbons and Stickers, circa; 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Campaign Letters, 1970 October-November (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Political Schedule and Notes, 1970 June (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Report on the Inquiry Completed by the ASI, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Program/Gridiron, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Frank McCoy – Dickey’s Carpets, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Winfield Dunn Transition – Personal File on Governor Dunn, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - GOP Material – Information Lists, 1970-1972 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - GOP Material – Information Lists, 1970-1972 (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - GOP Material – Nashville Association of Musicians, circa; 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - GOP Material – Directory of Public and Private Schools, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - GOP Material – Nashville Attorneys, circa; 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - GOP Material – Directory of Tennessee Municipal Officials, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - GOP Material – Nashville Businessmen, circa 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - GOP Material – General Sessions Judges, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - GOP Material – Chattanooga Businessmen – circa, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - GOP Material – Directory of Tennessee Doctors, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - GOP Material – Election Results – circa, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - GOP Material – Republican National Leadership Conference, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - GOP Material – Republican National Committee Professional Staff Conference, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - GOP Material – Tennessee Republican Party Folder, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series C: 1974 Campaign
    - Campaign Records
      - Primary Election –Research About Previous Primaries (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - A Study of the Political Climate in Tennessee –Study #1103, April 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - A Study of the Political Climate in Tennessee –Wave IV Study # 780, March 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - A Survey of the Political Climate in Tennessee –Wave V Study # 1282, January 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - State of Tennessee Political Opinions, October 21-23, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Election Results for the 1970 General Election (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Precincts by Major Groupings –General Election, 1970 (1 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Precincts by Major Groupings –General Election, 1970 (2 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Precincts by Major Groupings –General Election, 1970 (3 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Precincts by Major Groupings –General Election, 1970 (4 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - 1970 Census of Housing (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Records
      - 1970 Census of Population and Housing –Nashville/Davidson (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - 1970 Census of Population and Housing –Knoxville (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - 1970 County Business Patterns –Tennessee, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Election Returns for the General Election, November 7, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - General Election of 1972 Statistics in Tennessee (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Publications, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Opinion Poll –State of Tennessee, September 1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - “Gubernatorial Transition in Tennessee: The 1970-71 Experience” by Leonard Keelon Bradley Jr., 1973 Thesis (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Gallup Polls # 100-103, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Certification of Election Returns for Republican Primary Election, August 1, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Certification of Election Returns for Democrat Primary Election, August 1, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Certification of Election Returns for General Election, August 1, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Certification of Election Returns for General Election, November 5, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - 1974 Republican Primary –A Summary (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Tennessee Senate Races, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Records
      - Advertising (1 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Advertising (2 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Advertising (3 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Advertising (4 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Advertising (5 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Advertising –Alexander Brochures (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Office Rental (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - College Organizational Manual, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - County Board Recommendations –Republicans (1 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - County Board Recommendations –Republicans (2 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - County Board Recommendations –Republicans (3 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - County Judges in Tennessee –List (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - County Lists (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - County Republican Committees, 1974 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - County Republican Committees, 1974 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Evans/Novak Reports (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Forms Used During Campaign –Blank (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - General Information on Districts in Tennessee (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Maps of Tennessee (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous Campaign Materials (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Potential Contributors, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Precinct Quotas –Priority Precincts (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Precinct Quotas –Priority Precincts (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Precinct Workers –Memos (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Campaign Records
      - 1974 Primary Election –Democrat (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - 1974 Primary Election –Republican (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Primary Election Contact Lists (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - 1974 Primary – Priority Counties in GOP Primary (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Publicity for Campaign (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Projected Quotas (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Republican Primary Results (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - South Central Bell Telephone (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Speeches (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, February-July 1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, October 1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, November 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, December 1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, January 31-February 28, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, February 4-10, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Schedules –Lamar Alexander, 10-22, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)